(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
甘い　デコレーションケーキのような　街は　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
A city like a sweet decorated cake is Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
空が　くれる　コンフェッティは　冬のフェスタ祝う　天使の羽よ
The confetti falling from the sky are angel wings celebrating the winter festival
白銀の国へ　出かけるの　GO! GO! GO!
Heading to the silver country. GO! GO! GO!
雪の汽車が　街を駆け　CHOO! CHOO! CHOO!
The snow train runs through the town. CHOO! CHOO! CHOO!
絵本みたいな景色を　君に見せてあげるから
I'll show you a scenery like a picture book
願い込めて呪文　さぁ　唱えて
Make a wish and chant the spell
One, two, three!
A B C D ドレミファソラシ　マジカル　ミラクル　クル・ポッ！
A B C D Do-Re-Mi-Fa-Sol-La-Si, Magical Miracle, Kuru-Po!
甘い　デコレーションケーキのような　街は　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
A city like a sweet decorated cake is Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
空が　くれる　コンフェッティは　冬のフェスタ祝う　天使の羽よ
The confetti falling from the sky are angel wings celebrating the winter festival
ライトアップした　オーロラ色の街は　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
The illuminated aurora-colored city is Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
子供でいられたら　Three, two, one!
If only we could stay as children, Three, two, one!
Ladies and Gentlemen, Welcome to MelKiss!
ツンと　冷たい　季節も　好きになれるわ
I can even learn to love the biting cold season
アイスの魔法　解けないように　ヒュー・ヒュー・ヒュー
So the ice magic doesn't melt, Hew-Hew-Hew
ずっと　このままじゃダメなの　やっぱり　ドキドキしたいな
I can't stay like this forever, after all, I want my heart to race
未来　求め呪文　さぁ　唱えて
Seeking the future, chant the spell
One, two, three!
一二三四　水金地火木　マジカル　ミラクル　クル・ポッ！
1 2 3 4, Mercury Venus Earth Mars Jupiter, Magical Miracle, Kuru-Po!
ホップした　ウサギのような気分　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
Feeling like a hopping rabbit, Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
大地が　くれる　キャンディ食べたら　思い通り遊んでいけるよ
If I eat the candy the earth gives me, I can play as I wish
眩しい　白に染まる　ハート　君に　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
A heart dyed in dazzling white, to you, Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
大人のふりなんて　いいじゃん
Who cares about pretending to be an adult?
I hear the bell now, winter is coming! This is my world,
are you ready? Nanana fantastic! Snow cake magical!
Smile flavor magical! I see you feel my love, oh oh oh oh!
今日の　寒さも　忘れるように
So we can forget today's cold
悩みだって　悩みだって　凍らせて　消せる　魔力よ
It's a magic power that can freeze and erase even worries, even worries
A B C D ドレミファソラシ　マジカル　ミラクル　クル・ポッ！
A B C D Do-Re-Mi-Fa-Sol-La-Si, Magical Miracle, Kuru-Po!
甘い　デコレーションケーキのような　街は　スキ・ユキ・マジ・マジック
A city like a sweet decorated cake is Suki-Yuki-Maji-Magic
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
見てる？見てる？
Are you watching? Are you watching?
じゃーん！じゃじゃじゃーん！
Ta-da! Ta-da-da-da!
ちょこ先生のさっきのサンタ衣装と...
Choco-sensei's previous Santa outfit and...
...メル様の雪だるま衣装！
...Mel-sama's snowman outfit!
交換してみました！
We've swapped them!
イェーイ！可愛いでしょ？
Yay! Cute, right?
どうかな？どうかな？
How do we look? How do we look?
めちゃめちゃ可愛くない？この衣装！
Isn't this outfit super cute?!
可愛いよね。
It's cute, isn't it?
いっぱい写真撮って...
Take lots of photos...
...いっぱいちょこの感想ツイートしてほしいな。
...and I want you to tweet lots of impressions of Choco.
このハッシュタグで！
With this hashtag!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
このあともね、いっぱい楽しい曲が続くから...
Since many more fun songs follow after this...
...みんなもいっぱい声出して、お家でねサイリウムとか振って楽しんでね！
...everyone raise your voices and enjoy by waving glow sticks at home!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
じゃあ、ちょこ先生、早速次の曲行きますか？
Well, Choco-sensei, shall we move on to the next song?
いっちゃいますか？
Shall we do it?
レッツゴー！
Let's Go!
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that makes my heart skip a beat
パッと消えそうな心象が
A mental image that seems to vanish in a flash
ぼくあたしのファインダーを
Fills my viewfinder
満たしてキレイさ
And it's beautiful
どうでもいいけど
Though it doesn't really matter
いいね いいね
Like, like
バシャリ、キラリ、フワもたり
Snap, sparkle, fluffy and more
背伸び、天使は
Stretch, the angel is...
フワフワ自愛して欲が
Fuzzy self-love and desire...
「見せたい！見せたい！」クレッシェンド
Wanting to show off, wanting to show off, crescendo
流行り、つまり、似たり寄ったり
Trends, in short, more of the same
加工したスマイワールド
The processed world we live in
飾らない君を愛した熱も
Even the heat of loving the unadorned you
「いらない！いらない！」クレッシェンド
Is unnecessary, unnecessary, crescendo
味わう前に口に出ちゃう
Falling from my lips before I can even taste it
ラブはインスタント
Love is instant
君のハートすら
Even your heart
欲しくなっちゃう今日もバエスタシー
I start to want, today too, instastasy
こうやって加工欲加工すればたくさんいいねもらえるのか...
If I process it coolly like this, can I get lots of likes?
よし！ちょこも加工！どや！
Alright! Choco will process it too! How's that?!
あれ？やりすぎ？
Huh? Did I overdo it?
いいね いいね 愛してみても
Like, like, even if I try to love it
いいね いいね どうぞお好きに
Like, like, as you please
いいね いいね 実はどうでも
Like, like, it doesn't really matter
いいね いいね 好きも嫌いも
Like, like, whether I like or hate it
流行ファッションイマイチわからん
I don't really get current fashion trends
でもでもちょっと手を伸ばしておしゃれ
But, but, I'll reach out a bit and be stylish
あたしにだってできるはずなんだ
I should be able to do it too
まずははじめの第一歩
First, the first step
手軽に放送手軽に投稿
Easy broadcasting, easy posting
こんなのも出てるエフェクト
Effects like this are out there too
かけちゃえ上々したいのヘヴン
Apply them, feeling high, wanting heaven
思い立ったの即登録
Registered as soon as I thought of it
タグ付けする友達がいない
I have no friends to tag
位置情報は外せない
I can't remove the location info
これがSNSワールドの典例か
Is this the law of the SNS world?
必死にサバイバル&エフォート
Desperate survival and effort
あたしはここだよ見てくれ世間
I'm right here, world, look at me
気になったなら押して渡れでsay
If you're curious, press it and cross over, say
いいね
Like
舌の音で
With the sound of the tongue
跳ねる衝動だけでいいや
Just the bouncing impulse is enough
なんて思うのにさ
Or so I think, but...
入る方向までついつい追っちゃうよ
I end up following even the direction of entry
そう！こういう新しいものがいいねを稼げるのか！
I see! So things like this can earn likes!
ならメルはこの新作のフラペチーノを投稿！
Then Mel will post this new Frappuccino!
あれ？これ中身こぼれてる！あたたた...！
Huh? The contents are spilling! Ouch ouch ouch...!
いいね いいね もっとくれたら
Like, like, if you give me more
いいな いいな 不純だって
It'd be nice, even if it's impure
いいよ インスタント魔法で
It's okay, with instant magic
僕らちょっと繋がれるんだ
We can connect a little
どうでもいいから
Because it doesn't matter
どうでもいいけど
Whatever, but...
やっぱ撮っちゃう
I'll take a photo anyway
派手なスイーツ
Flashy sweets
いいね いいね
Like it, like it
Vocal: 癒月ちょこ
Vocal: Yuzuki Choco
Vocal: 夜空メル
Vocal: Yozora Mel
Movie: 甘いなつ
Movie: Amai Natsu
Illustrations: 日紙
Illustrations: Hikami
きらり光る白い雪が
The sparkling white snow
Snow Fairy Story
作詞・作曲: 40mP
Lyrics/Composition: 40mP
少しずつ街を染めてゆく
Is gradually staining the town
さあ 二人で奏でるメロディ
Come, the melody we play together
探しに出かけよう
Let's go find it
この冬最後の雪が
The last snow of this winter
僕らの街に舞い降りた
Has fallen on our town
二人が歩いた道の
Of the path we walked together
足跡を消してしまう
Footprints are being erased
冷たい空気吸い込んで
Inhaling the cold air
泣き出しそうな空を見た
I looked at the sky that seemed about to cry
明日の朝には二人
By tomorrow morning, the two of us
別々の場所へ歩き出す
Will start walking to different places
臆病すぎた僕は
I was too cowardly
大事なことも言えず
I couldn't even say the important things
震える君のその手を
Even taking your trembling hand...
握ることさえも
I couldn't even...
きらり光る白い雪が
The sparkling white snow
少しずつ街を染めてゆく
Is gradually staining the town
さあ 二人で奏でるメロディ
Come, the melody we play together
探しに出かけよう
Let's go find it
長い夢が覚める前に
Before waking up from the long dream
この思い君に届けたい
I want to deliver these feelings to you
きっと また新しい歌声が
Surely, a new singing voice again
この空に舞い降りる
Will fall upon this sky
この冬最後の風が
The last wind of this winter
僕らの街を吹き抜けた
Has blown through our town
枯れ木に宿る蕾が
The buds dwelling on the withered trees
春の訪れを告げる
Announce the arrival of spring
おどけた顔でごまかして
Disguising with a joking face
うつむく僕をからかった
You teased me as I looked down
去年の冬より少し
A little bit more
大人びた君のその笑顔
Grown-up than last winter, your smile
不器用すぎた僕は
I was too clumsy
大事なことを見落とし
Overlooking the important things
零れる君の涙に
Even noticing...
気づくことさえも
Your overflowing tears...
できなくて
I couldn't
ひらり落ちる白い雪が
The white snow falling lightly
少しずつ頬を染めてゆく
Is gradually staining your cheeks
もう 二人で奏でるリズム
Already, the rhythm we play together
途切れないように
So it doesn't break
ずっと きらり光る白い雪が
Always, the sparkling white snow
少しずつ空へとけてゆく
Is gradually melting into the sky
ねえ 二人で奏でたメロディ
Hey, the melody we played together
忘れはしないよ
I won't forget it
長い夢が覚める頃に
Around the time when the long dream wakes
君はもう消えてしまうけど
Even though you will have disappeared already
きっと また懐かしい歌声が
Surely, a nostalgic singing voice again
新しい未来で
In a new future...
光り輝く雪になって
Will become shining snow
この空に舞い降りる
And fall upon this sky
舞い降りる...
Fluttering down...
やがて...
And eventually...
目の前に舞い降りる...
...fluttering down before my eyes...
じゃあね、ここからは...
Well then, from here on...
うん。
Yeah.
なんと...
Lo and behold...
撮影コーナーに入ります！
We're starting the photo corner!
やったー！
Yay!
イェーイ！
てことで、えー、ホロメンのね、何人かにちょっと来てもらって...
So, we've asked a few Hololive members to come on...
おっと！
Oh!
メルたちにとって欲しいポーズを指定してもらってですね、
And have them specify poses they want us to do.
可愛いポーズをいっぱい撮りたいと思いますので、ちょっとね着替えていきたいと思います。
We want to take lots of cute photos, so we're going to go and change now.
はい。
Yes.
ちょっとだけ待っててくださいね。
Please wait just a moment.
待っててね。
Wait for us, okay?
リンリンリンリンリンリン... イェーイ！
Ring ring ring ring ring ring... Yay!
イェーイ！
Yay!
着替えてきたよ！
We've changed!
みんなお待たせ。
Sorry for the wait, everyone.
お待たせ。
Sorry for the wait.
メルサンタと...
I'm Mel Santa, and...
チョコサンタです！
I'm Choco Santa!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあね、早速一人目お呼びしたいと思います。
Well then, let's call our first guest right away.
はい。
Okay.
一人目はこの方！
The first person is... this member!
キアラケ！
Tis Kiara!
メリークリスマス！メリークリスマス皆様！キアラちゃん！
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas, everyone! Kiara-chan!
メリーフッケリークリスマス！
Merry Huckery Christmas!
え、メリーフッケリークリスマス？
Eh, Merry Huckery Christmas?
ホーホーホー、サンタクロースの二人ですか？可愛い。
Ho ho ho, are you two Santa Clauses? So cute.
そうだよ、だからチキン頂戴。
That's right, so give us some chicken.
そうよ、寄こしなさい。
That's right, hand it over.
だめよ！
No way!
寄こせ、ほら、寄こせ、ほらほらほらほら！
Hand it over, come on, hand it over, come on, come on!
私不死鳥なんでチキンはちょっと渡せられないんですけども。
I'm a phoenix, so I can't exactly give you chicken.
ケチー！
Stingy!
えー、海外のミームを真似してもらいたいなと思ってきましたけど、どうですかね？
I came here thinking I'd like you to imitate some overseas memes. What do you think?
ミーム？いいよ。
Memes? Sure.
ミーム、そうそうそう。とある海外のアニメのポーズを真似してもらいたいです、二人で。できるかな？
Memes, yeah, yeah, yeah. I want you two to imitate a pose from a certain overseas anime. Can you do it?
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
そしたら、一人、死に掛けるようなキャラクターが必要なんですけど、死に掛けたい人誰ですか？
Alright then, I need one of you to be a character who's about to die. Who wants to be about to die?
じゃ、チョコ死に掛けます。
Then Choco will be about to die.
オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, okay.
死に掛けチョコ先生、床に、えー、倒れて欲しいです、まず。
Dying Choco-sensei, first, I want you to collapse on the floor.
バーン。
Bam.
そうそうそうそう。え、そして、仰向きですね。体、そうそうそう、いい感じ。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. And then, face up. Your body, yeah, yeah, yeah, looking good.
で、そうしたら、メル先輩には、チョコ先生の隣に来て欲しいんですけど。
And then, Mel-senpai, I want you to come next to Choco-sensei.
ここ？
Here?
そうそこそこ、可愛い、可愛い、可愛い。
Yeah, right there. Cute, cute, cute.
で、隣でしゃがんで欲しいです。
And then I want you to crouch down next to her.
はい。
Okay.
そうそんな感じ、もうちょっと近くかな？
Yeah, like that. Maybe a bit closer?
イェス、イェス、イェス。で、そこで、えーと、考えろチョコ、考えろみたいなポーズ取って欲しい。そういうことです。
Yes, yes, yes. And there, take a pose like "Think Choco, Think!". That's it.
もうバッチリです！台詞だけ言ってもらいたいな。あの、英語で。
Perfect! Now I just want you to say the line. In English.
"Think Choco Think" って言って欲しい、怒った顔で。
I want you to say "Think, Choco, think!" with an angry face.
怒って...
Angry...
Think, Choco, think!
おおー！完璧！
Ooh! Perfect!
これをね、レディットでいっぱい載せてもらえそう。レディットぷくチョコぷりん。
I bet this will get posted a lot on Reddit. Reddit Puku Choco Purin!
オッケー、オッケー。もう一個あるけど、もう一個の方はもうちょっと簡単だと思って。
Okay, okay. There's one more, but I think this one is a bit easier.
えー、また隣に立って欲しいです。
I'd like you to stand next to each other again.
はい。
Okay.
で、チョコ先生、えーと、右腕をメル先輩の背中に乗せて欲しい。
And Choco-sensei, I want you to put your right arm on Mel-senpai's back.
そうそうそう、え、後ろ、後ろで。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, behind, behind.
で、左腕は、何か、メル先輩に何か遠いものを見せてるように、え、そうそうそうそう。
And with your left arm, as if you're showing Mel-senpai something far away... yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
で、チョコ先生は、嬉しい顔で。メル先輩は、怖い顔で。"ヤバい"みたいな。"マジかよ"みたいな。
And Choco-sensei, with a happy face. Mel-senpai, with a scared face. Like "Oh no!" or "Are you serious?"
泣いちゃう。
I'm gonna cry.
そうそうそうそうそう。これね、とある映画の有名な映画のミームでございます。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. This is a meme from a certain famous movie.
もう完璧、完璧！パチパチパチ。
Perfect, perfect! Clap clap clap.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
多分レディットで回します、ありがとうございました！
I'll probably post these on Reddit, thank you!
よろしくレディット。
Please take care of us, Reddit.
楽しい！
This is fun!
キアラちゃんありがとう！
Kiara-chan, thank you!
ありがとうー！メリークリスマス！
Thank you! Merry Christmas!
はあー、キアラちゃん楽しかったね。
Whew, Kiara-chan was fun, wasn't she?
うん、ありがとう。
Yeah, thank you.
ということで...
And so...
2人目はね、また衣装着替えようと思うので
For our second guest, we're going to change outfits again.
お、着替えていきたいと思います！
Oh, we're going to go change!
生着替えタイムです！
It's live-changing time!
まったねー！
See ya!
しばし待たれよ！
Wait just a moment!
タッタラー！イェーイ！
Ta-da! Yay!
着替えてきたよー！
We're changed!
どうかな？
How do we look?
雪だるメルと...
Snowman Mel and...
雪だるまチョコです。です！
Snowman Choco. Indeed!
ということで、2人目早速呼んでいきましょう！
And so, let's call our second guest right away!
はーい
Okay!
それじゃあ、2人目...
And now, for guest number two...
もしもーし！
Hello?
はーい
Hello!
あ、もぐもぐ〜おかゆ〜！
Ah, mogu mogu~ Okayu~!
おかゆちゃーん！
Okayu-chan!
おかゆ様ーー！
Okayu-sama!
メルトちゃん、ヤッホー！遊びに来たよ！
Mel-chan, Yahoo! I've come to play!
ありがとー！待ってたよー！
Thank you! We've been waiting for you!
めっちゃさ、その雪だるま衣装、めっちゃ可愛い
I have to say, those snowman outfits are so cute.
え、本当に！？嬉しい！
Oh, really!? We're so happy!
やったー。なんか雪だるまが1, 2, 3... 4つぐらい付いてる？
Yay. Are there like 1, 2, 3... four snowmen on them?
付いてる付いてる！
There are! There are!
6つかも知れないけどね
There might even be six of them.
6個ある、6個。1, 2, 3, 4, 5... 6個だ！やったー！
There are six, six. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5... there are six! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
2人にさ、僕が指定したポーズをしてもらえるって聞いたんだけど...
I heard that you two would do whatever poses I ask for...
そうなんです！もちろん！何何？
That's right! Of course! What is it?
なんかチョコ先生とメルちゃんだとNGがなさそうだよね
It feels like there are no NGs with Choco-sensei and Mel-chan.
なんでもやっちゃうよ！
We'll do anything!
任せてほしい！
Leave it to us!
どうしようかな？やっぱちょっとくっついて可愛いてぇてぇポーズをしてもらいたいから...
What should I pick? I want you to get close for a cute 'teete' pose...
じゃあ、めっちゃギューって近づいて...
So, get really, really close together...
うわー！これはヤバいです！これはヤバいです！
Whoa! This is amazing! This is amazing!
近づいてどうするの？おかゆ様
What should we do now that we're close, Okayu-sama?
やばいやばいやばい... 何何！？
Oh boy, oh boy... what's this!?
何何？
What? What is it?
正面向いてください、正面向いてください
Please face forward, please face forward.
何がヤバいのー？
What's so amazing?
じゃあ、正面向いてにゃんにゃんポーズしてください
Then, face forward and do a 'nyan-nyan' pose.
はーい
Okay!
にゃん！にゃんにゃん！
Nyan! Nyan-nyan!
待って、さっきの刺激が強すぎて声枯れちゃったよ
Wait, that was so intense I've gone hoarse.
おかゆちゃーん！
Okayu-chan!
可愛い？にゃんにゃんにゃん。おかゆ猫の仲間だにゃ
Is it cute? Nyan nyan nyan. We're Okayu-cat's friends now, nyan.
可愛い。白チョコと白メル、養ってくれるにゃ？
So cute. White Choco and White Mel, will you take care of me, nyan?
いいにゃよ！2匹養ってあげるにゃよ！
Sure, nyan! We'll take care of both of you, nyan!
やったにゃよ！嬉しいにゃー！一緒に寝てくれるにゃ？
Yay, nyan! I'm so happy, nyan! Will you sleep with me, nyan?
いいにゃよー！
Of course, nyan!
なんでも全肯定おかゆちゃん
All-affirming Okayu-chan.
いや、ウェンちゃんを養うのなんか荷が重そうだな...
But taking care of Mel-chan and Choco-sensei seems like it might be a lot of work...
えー、何を言っていらっしゃるの！
Hey, what are you saying!?
メル、そんなに手間かかんないよ！
I don't take that much effort!
確かにチョコ先生が荷が重そうやな
Choco-sensei definitely seems like a lot of work.
確かに確かに
True, true.
いやいや、チョコはちゃんと温めて寝てあげるわよ
No no, I'll keep you nice and warm when we sleep.
本当に？カイロだ、カイロ
Really? Like a heat pack, a heat pack.
チョコカイロ！
Choco-heat pack!
にゃんにゃん！
Nyan nyan!
え、どうしようかな... じゃあ次は、後ろ向いて...
Hmm, what should I pick next... Okay, turn around...
後ろ向いて...
Turn around...
お尻フリフリとかどうですか？
How about wiggling your butts?
お尻フリフリ！おかよフリフリ！
Wiggle wiggle! Okayo wiggle wiggle!
わ、ちょっとカメラマンさん際どいです！下げすぎ下げすぎ！
Whoa, Mr. Cameraman, that's a bit too low! Too low, too low!
可愛い！
So cute!
じゃあ最後は、こっち向いてカメラに向かって投げキッスでお願いします
Then finally, face the camera and give us a blown kiss, please.
はーい
Okay!
おかゆ大好きよ！チュッ！
I love you Okayu! *Kiss*
おかゆちゃーん、大好き！チュッ！
Okayu-chan, I love you! *Kiss*
うわー！可愛すぎる！
Waaah! Too cute!
やったー！ありがとおかゆちゃん！
Yay! Thank you Okayu-chan!
もう限界です、さようなら！
I'm at my limit, goodbye!
バイバイ！またね！ありがとう！にゃんにゃん！バイにゃん！
Bye-bye! See ya! Thank you! Nyan nyan! Bye nyan!
はあ、おかゆちゃん、いつも通り癒やされるね
Sigh, Okayu-chan is as healing as always.
じゃあ最後の生着替え行きましょうか
Then, let's go for the final live change.
はーい、行ってきまーす！
Okay, we're off!
にゃんにゃんにゃんにゃん...
Nyan nyan nyan nyan...
タッタラー！お待たせ！
Ta-da! Sorry for the wait!
やっぱ最後はこの衣装だよね
The last part has to be in this outfit, after all.
まあまあ、私たちアイドルですからね！
Well, well, we are idols, after all!
ということで、最後の曲...
And so, for our final song...
お呼びしますか？
Shall we call her?
誰なのかなー？
I wonder who it is...
誰かな、もしもし？
Who is it? Hello?
もしもーし！
Hellooo!
こんらみー！
Kon-Lamy!
さあ！
Now!
待ってた待ってた！ 待ってたよー
We were waiting! I was waiting!
いや、もう、そのリボンちょっと可愛すぎやしませんか？
Seriously, aren't those ribbons just a bit too cute?
そうなんですよー お揃いなの！とっても可愛い！
That's right! They're matching! Very cute!
めちゃめちゃ可愛い、もなこさんありがとうございます。
Super cute! Thank you, Monako-san.
ありがとー！ 嬉しいー！
Thank you! So happy!
で、なんか今日はもうラミィの好きなポーズを二人がとってくれるって聞いたんですけど。
And I heard that today the two of you would do poses that I like.
いやー、任せましたよプロデューサー！ プロデューサー！ プロデューサー！
Yeah, we're in your hands, Producer! Producer! Producer!
え、じゃあ早速、いいですか？ はーい。
Well then, can we start right away? Yes.
え、じゃあちょっと二人が向かい合わせみたいな感じで、膝立ちで座ってもらっていいですか？
Well then, could the two of you face each other and sit on your knees?
膝立ち？
On our knees?
あ、そうそうそう、あ、いい、いい、いいよいいよ。
Ah, yeah yeah yeah, ah, good, good, good good.
で、こうちょっと二人が抱き合う感じで。
And then, kind of like you're hugging each other.
あー、そうそうそうそう。
Ah, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
からの、チョコ先生ちょっとこっちを向いて、あ、上目遣いたまらん。カメラマンさんいいよ！
And then, Choco-sensei look over here a bit... Ah, that upturned look is irresistible. Cameraman, looking good!
あ、いいよいいよ！ あー近い！ 可愛いー！
Ah, looking good! Ah, so close! Cute!
ちょっとそこでなんかドキドキメリークリスマスみたいな、一言もらってもいいですか？
Could I get a word from you there, like a heart-pounding "Merry Christmas"?
近い... メリークリスマス、チョコ先生。
So close... Merry Christmas, Choco-sensei.
メリークリスマス、メル様。大好き。
Merry Christmas, Mel-sama. I love you.
あーありがとうございますありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you, thank you very much!
そしたらね、ちょっとその可愛い感じ、あ、たまらん。立ってもらって。
Then, that cute feeling... Ah, irresistible. Please stand up.
はい。やっぱね、二人にちょっとこう下からも見たいので。下から？近づいてもらって。
Yes. As I thought, I want to see you two from below as well. From below? Please come closer.
はい。二人にこう近づいてもらって、カメラマンさん下から。煽る感じで。
Yes. Come closer together, cameraman from below. In a low-angle shot.
あー、いいよいいよ、あ、いいその煽り顔、煽り顔で。
Ah, good good, ah, good, those low-angle faces, with the low-angle faces.
あーいい、いいですよたまらん。
Ah, good, it's good, irresistible.
かかってこいよ。 かかってこいよ、いいですか？ かかってこいよ。
Come at me. "Come at me," is that okay? Come at me.
かかってこいよ。 かかってこいよ。
Come at me. Come at me.
あーもっとこのちょっとギリギリを攻める感じにこうちょっと煽ってもらっていいですか下からカメラマンさん。
Ah, can you provoke a bit more like you're pushing the limit, cameraman, from below?
もうちょい下ですね。はい、もうちょいもうちょい。あ、ちょっと大きいものでメル先輩の顔が見えない。
A bit lower. Yes, a bit more, a bit more. Ah, Mel-senpai's face is hidden by something big.
ちょっと下から見たらブサイクになっちゃうでしょ。あ、ごめんなさいすみません。
Seeing from below makes us look ugly, doesn't it? Ah, sorry, excuse me.
ちょっと引きで、もうちょい下、もうちょい下。プラス引いて引いて、もうちょい引いて引いて引いて。
A bit wider, a bit lower, a bit lower. Plus pull back, pull back... pull back a bit more...
あ、ちょっと、あーダメダメ！ ダメダメダメダメダメダメ！
Ah, wait, ah, no no! No no no no no no!
メルの方が身長小さいから見えちゃう！
Mel is shorter so it'll show!
これちょっとカメラマンさんもうちょっとギリギリのところで足を見せてもらう感じがいいんですけど、引いてもらったほうがいいですね。
I'd like the cameraman to show the legs at the very edge, but it would be better if you pulled back a bit.
あ、そうそうそうそう。あ、メル先輩、あぶないあぶない。
Ah, yeah yeah yeah yeah. Ah, Mel-senpai, watch out, watch out.
メル様だんだんお尻、お尻見えちゃう！そんな大胆に！あーダメ！
Mel-sama, your butt's starting to show! So bold! Ah, no!
もうダメだ、死んでしまう... もうありがとうございます！
It's no use, I'm going to die... Thank you very much!
そしたらね、もうじゃあ、とびっきりの笑顔で、メリークリスマスと言ってもらってもいいですか？
Well then, could you say "Merry Christmas" with your best smiles?
はーい。
Yes.
ラミィちゃん、メリークリスマス！
Lamy-chan, Merry Christmas!
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
あーメリークリスマス！！ ラミィさん、ありがとうございましたー！
Ah, Merry Christmas!! Lamy-san, thank you very much!
ありがとー。
Thank you.
じゃあ、次の曲行こうかな？
Well, shall we go to the next song?
いっちゃおうかなー！
Let's go!
聞いて　会いたいのに飛んでって
Listen, I want to see you so I'm flying there
少し困るくらいに　甘えたり
Maybe being a bit too clingy
ちゃんと聞いてみて　受け取って
Listen properly and receive it
甘く解けちゃうような　時を
A time that seems to melt sweetly
疲れてる顔して
You look tired
いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You're always working so hard
もう全て任せて
Just leave it all to me
全部食べてあげようか
Shall I eat it all up for you?
余所見なんて嫌だよ
I hate it when you look away
ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
You have to look properly this way
目と目が合うでしょ
Our eyes meet, right?
照れちゃうくらい　見つめてね
Stare at me until it's embarrassing
ひとつ　夢中にさせて
One, make me crazy about you
ふたつ　見つけてね
Two, find me, okay?
…虜にしちゃうの
...and captivate you.
心拍数 急上昇
My heart rate is soaring!
みんな夢中に ズッキュンド
Everyone's infatuated, Zukkyun-do!
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけ
Pain, pain, fly away!
不安な顔より笑顔見せて
Show me a smile instead of a worried face.
めちゃときめいて受け取って
Feel the flutter and receive it,
甘いチョコのような時を
a time like sweet chocolate.
ここに痛いの痛いのもう困っちゃう
It hurts right here, oh, I'm in trouble.
不意打ちにチョコっとドキめく
A sudden little sweet heart-throb.
じらしちゃうわよだめ、もうちょっと
I'll tease you, no, just a bit more.
君の声を もっと聞かせて
Let me hear your voice more.
不安なんて抱えてらしくないなんて思ってた
I thought it wasn't like me to be carrying such anxiety.
全部、全部、丸ごと包み込んで
I'll wrap it all, all up,
溶かしてあげる
and melt it for you.
みんな、メルキスライブ楽しんでる？
Everyone, are you enjoying Melkiss Live?
もっともっとみんなと一緒にいたいから
I want to be with you all more and more,
最後まで楽しんで見てってねー！
so please enjoy watching until the very end!
どうしたって何したって気持ちは同じなんだよね
No matter what happens, no matter what I do,
my feelings remain the same.
ここだってどこだって想いは伝わるから
Because my feelings will reach you,
whether here or anywhere else.
声にして、文字にして、勇気出して伝えてよ
Put it into words, put it into text,
be brave and tell me.
今日だって、いつだって、あー、愛してるの
Today, always, ah, I love you.
Ah, Ah... Tweet dreams...
隠さないで、ちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me properly,
君のこと全部を 頂戴
give me everything about you.
きっと痛いの痛いの飛んでって
I'm sure the pain will fly away,
過ごしちゃうくらい お願い
so much so that we'll lose track of time, please.
高鳴る心聞いてみて、感じてほしいの
Listen to my pounding heart, I want you to feel it.
会いたいわ すぐ飛んでって
I want to see you, I'll fly to you right now,
過ごしちゃうくらい お願い
so much so that we'll lose track of time, please.
めちゃときめいて受け取って
Feel the flutter and receive it,
甘く蕩けちゃうよな時を
a time that'll melt you sweetly.
隣にいたいから
Because I want to be by your side.
Ah, Ah... Tweet dreams...
ChocoLove!
私のこと 知ってますか？
Do you know who I am?
可愛く見えてますか？
Do I look cute to you?
私の歌 どうだろうな？
How about my singing?
うまく歌えてますか？
Am I singing well?
衣装だとか メイクだとか
My outfit, my makeup...
可愛く見えてますか？
do they make me look cute?
振り付けとか ファンサとかも
My choreography and fan service,
喜んでもらえますか？
are they making you happy?
手が冷たくなって 足は震えてる
My hands have gone cold, and my legs are trembling.
それでも戦いたい アイドルだから
But I still want to fight, because I'm an idol.
馬鹿にする奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who mock me,
蔑まれるのも嫌いだ
I hate being looked down upon.
アイドルなんかという言葉を
Don't say things like 'just an idol'
見てもいないくせに言うな
when you haven't even seen me.
頑張りを笑うな 努力を否定するな
Don't laugh at my hard work, don't deny my efforts.
夢売事とか強制するな
Don't force me to 'sell dreams'.
アイドルなんかという言葉は
Words like 'just an idol'...
この世で一番大嫌いだ
I hate them more than anything in this world.
プライベート見えないから
You can't see my private life,
分からないと思います
so I don't think you can understand.
性格とか
As for my personality...
悪いほうです 騙しちゃっていますか？
...it's on the bad side. Have I deceived you?
でも本気です 本気なんです
But I'm serious, I'm really serious.
ありのままの私を
About the real me...
好きになって 推してください
...please love and support me.
それってわがままですか？
Is that selfish of me?
きっと可愛くない
I'm surely not cute.
全部分かってる
I know all of it.
それでも好かれてたい
But I still want to be loved.
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol.
低い奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who look down on others.
言い訳ばかりも嫌いだ
I also hate those who just make excuses.
こんなもんかという言葉を
Words like "is this all you've got?"
軽々しく口にするな
Don't say them so lightly.
勝手に限界決めるな
Don't decide the limit on your own.
笑いものになんてするな
Don't make me a laughingstock.
アイドルなんとかという言葉は
The word "idol" or whatever...
この世で一番大嫌いだ
...I hate it the most in this world.
強い強い心に誓え
Vow to your strong, strong heart.
誇り高きアイドル
A proud idol.
目指そうぜ
Let's aim for it!
応援がなければ活動できない
I can't work without your support.
好きなことばかりじゃ生きてはいけない
I can't live just by doing what I like.
元気あげるはずが
I'm supposed to give you energy...
もらってばかりだし 恩返しできる日まで待ってて
...but I'm only receiving it. Wait for the day I can repay you.
歓声が減っても
Even if the cheers decrease...
飽きられちゃっても
...even if you get tired of me...
それでも笑っていたい
...I still want to be smiling.
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol.
厚いファンの愛があって
There is the thick love of fans,
スタッフさんの愛があって
there is the love of staff members,
いつも家族の愛があって
there is always the love of family...
生きてる
...and I'm living.
アイドル
Idol.
馬鹿にする奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who make fun of us.
見下されるのも嫌いだ
I also hate being looked down upon.
アイドルなんとかという言葉を
The word "idol" or whatever...
見てもいないくせに言うな
...don't say it when you haven't even seen us.
頑張りもせずというな
Don't say we're not working hard.
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force images on us.
アイドルなんとかという言葉は
The word "idol" or whatever...
この世で一番大嫌いだ
...I hate it the most in this world.
君色シグナル / Covered by メルキス
Kimiiro Signal / Covered by Mel-Kiss
放課後 二人で過ごした教室
The classroom where we spent time together after school.
机の上 夢中で弾む君の声
Your voice bouncing excitedly above the desk.
鈍感な君のその態度が
That attitude of yours, so insensitive...
いつも私を
...it always makes me...
意地悪にさせるの
...act mean.
ひとりぼっちだと思う時もある
There are times when I think I'm all alone.
涙止められない日もある
There are days when I can't stop the tears.
本当の私を
I want you to...
見つめてほしいの
...look at the real me.
きっと伝わると信じているよ
I believe it will surely reach you.
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
Because you never, ever change...
私が何回も何回も
...I'll send you signals...
シグナル送ってあげる
...over and over again.
夢見たあの場所目指して
Aiming for that place I dreamed of...
くじけそうな時も
...even when I'm about to give up...
頑張れそうだよ
...I feel like I can do my best...
君がいるから
...because you are here.
二人歩くいつもの帰り道
The usual way home where the two of us walk.
名前がない気持ちが芽生え始めてる
Feelings without a name are starting to sprout.
だけど踏み出すための
But the courage to...
勇気は
...take a step forward...
少しだけまだ遠くにありそう
...still seems to be a little bit far away.
何も持っていなかった
To me, who had nothing...
私に
君がくれた心の鍵は
...the key to my heart that you gave me...
せーの！
One, two!
オークルで眠ってたつぼみに
To the buds that were sleeping in ochre
春の日差しを届けて
Deliver the spring sunshine
くれる
To me
君をいつだっていつだって
Always, always thinking
想ってるから
About you
きっとねいつかいつかちゃんと
I hope that someday, someday
わかってほしい
You'll understand
二人で描いた未来を
The future we painted together
もっと近い距離で見つめられるように
So we can look at it from even closer
夢見てるから
Because I'm dreaming
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
メル様！これからもよろしくね！
Lady Mel! Looking forward to working with you from now on too!
チョコ先生、こちらこそ！
Choco-sensei, same here!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あの日触れた君のシグナル
The signal from you I touched that day
始まりの扉が開くよ
The door to the beginning is opening
あのね
You know...
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないでね
Please always, always stay the same
私に何回も何回もシグナル
Send me signals again and again
送ってほしい
I want you to send them
輝くあの虹のように
Like that shining rainbow
涙のあとも奇跡に変えるよ
I'll turn even the traces of tears into miracles
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
Because you're always, always the same
私が何回も何回もシグナル
I'll send signals again and again
送ってあげる
I'll send them to you
夢見たあの丘目指して
Aiming for that hill I dreamed of
挫けそうな時も頑張れそうだよ
Even when I'm about to give up, I feel like I can do my best
君がいるから
Because you are here
イェーイ！
Yay!
ここまでいっぱい曲聴いてもらったけど、みんなどうだった？どうだったかなー？
We've listened to a lot of songs so far, but how was it everyone? How was it~?
おおー！めっちゃ言ってくれるじゃん！
Oh! You guys are saying so much!
えー、そんなに良かった？チョコ嬉しい！
Eh, was it that good? Choco's so happy!
メルもめっちゃ嬉しい！ありがとう！ありがとう！
Mel's really happy too! Thank you! Thank you!
でね、でもうそろそろ終盤になってきたんだけど... えー、早い...
And, well, we're getting close to the end... Eh, so soon...
ここで、なんと重大発表です！
And now, we have a major announcement!
なんと、なんと！メルキス3周年記念グッズが発売されます！
Believe it or not! Mel-Kiss 3rd Anniversary commemorative goods will be on sale!
やったー！うー、すごい！イェーイ！
Hooray! Ooh, amazing! Yay!
まず、一つ目は... うん。
First, the first item is... Yep.
コップ！私たちとお揃いのメルキスコップが、こちら！
A cup! A Mel-Kiss cup matching ours, right here!
こちら！かわいい！かわいい！
Right here! It's so cute! So cute!
一緒にKPしよう！乾杯！乾杯！
Let's KP together! Cheers! Cheers!
そして、二つ目は、こちら！
And then, the second item is this!
じゃーん！メルキスの可愛いロゴが入ったTシャツ！
Ta-da! A T-shirt with the cute Mel-Kiss logo on it!
え、これ寝巻きとかに着れる？
Eh, can I wear this as pajamas or something?
うんうん！お出かけも一緒！黒と白があるよ！
Yeah! Wear it out too! It comes in black and white!
いや、もう二色ね、揃えちゃうもんねチョコ。
No, Choco's definitely getting both colors.
メルも揃えちゃうもんね。おそろっちしちゃう？
Mel's getting both too. Shall we match?
ペアるっく？双子コーデでペアるっく？ペアるっくも出来るよ！
Matching looks? Matching in twin outfits? You can do matching looks too!
最高じゃん！最高！
That's the best! The best!
そして、三つ目！TAYA先生描き下ろし、メルキスアクリルジオラマスタンド！
And the third one! A Mel-Kiss acrylic diorama stand, newly drawn by TAYA-sensei!
イェーイ！え、めっちゃめちゃ可愛い！やばくない？
Yay! Eh, it's so incredibly cute! Isn't it crazy?
やばいよね！みんな見て！このサンタ衣装！
It is crazy! Everyone look! These Santa outfits!
今回はオリジナルで考えていただいたんですよ！めっちゃ可愛いでしょう？可愛い！
They were designed specially for this! It's so cute, right? Cute!
メルたちをお家にお迎えしてね。してくれるよね？
Please welcome Mel and Choco into your home. You will, won't you?
さらに！今回は数量限定で、メルキス二人の直筆サイン入り全部セットが販売されるよ！
Furthermore! This time, a full set including hand-signed cards from both of us will be available in limited quantities!
ガ、ガチ？
Re... Really?
ガチ！
Really!
ガチ？
Really?
ガチ。
Really.
しかも、全部セットには、
What's more, the full set includes
メルキス撮り下ろしASMRボイスも付いてくるよ！
a newly recorded MelKiss ASMR voice!
な、な、な、なんだってー！
Wh-wh-wh-what?!
21時から、
From 21:00,
販売開始となるので、なんと今から、
sales will begin, so starting right now,
運営さんが概要欄にURLを貼ってくれます！
the staff will put the URL in the description!
わあー！
Wow!
ただし、
However,
このURL、21時からしか開けないので、
the URL won't work until 21:00,
皆様、待機よろしくお願いしますね。
so everyone, please wait until then.
ただしよー。
However!
待機よろしく！
Please wait!
しかもこの直筆サイン入りセット、
And this hand-signed set
数量限定だから、早めにね！
is limited quantity, so be quick!
早めに？
Quickly?
なくなっちゃったら、うちらのサインもらえなくなっちゃうからね。
If it runs out, you won't get our signatures.
な、なんてことなんだ...！
Wh-what a tragedy...!
お願いします！
Please!
もう、最後までドキドキ見るしかないじゃないか、この配信！
We'll just have to watch this stream excitedly until the end!
どうぞよろしくお願いします。
Thank you for your support.
ということで、チョコ先生、
So, Choco-sensei,
今日のこのライブ、
today's live,
何がコンセプトだったっけ？
what was the concept again?
いやもう、そんなの決まってるじゃない！
I mean, it's obvious!
私とメル様の、スウェット・ドロップス・クリスマス・ライブよ！
It's mine and Mel-sama's Sweat Drops Christmas Live!
あー、うん、そうなんだけど、
Ah, yeah, that's true, but
それもそうなんだけど、もっと大事な... ほら！
that's true, but there's something more important... look!
ついに婚姻届に書いてくれることになった？
Did you finally decide to sign the marriage certificate?
ちょっと惜しいけど違うよ！
That's close, but no!
惜しい？
Close?
違う！何、何、何？
No! What, what, what?
メルキスの3周年記念だよ！
It's MelKiss's 3rd anniversary!
え、もうチョコたち3周年経ったの？
Eh, has it already been 3 years for us?
そうだよ！
Yes!
それってさ、すごいことじゃない？
Isn't that amazing?
え、ってことは、3周年記念で、こんな素敵なステージも用意してくれたの？
Eh, so for our 3rd anniversary, they prepared such a wonderful stage?
そうだよ！
Yes!
チョコたちがクリスマス3周年ライブやりたいやりたいって言ってたから、
Because we kept saying we wanted to do a 3rd-anniversary Christmas live,
見て、こちら！
look at this!
なんと、クリスマスツリー！
Look, a Christmas tree!
クリスマスツリーに、プレゼント、可愛い！
A Christmas tree and presents, so cute!
みんな気づいてた？可愛いでしょ？
Did everyone notice? Isn't it cute?
今回運営さん色々準備いただいて、本当にありがとうございます、スタッフの皆様！
The staff prepared so much this time, thank you very much!
衣装もめっちゃ可愛かったよね！
The costumes were super cute too, right?
後でみんな感想とか色々待ってます！
We're waiting for everyone's thoughts later!
ハッシュタグいっぱい呟いてね！トレンド入りさせろー！
Tweet using the hashtag! Let's get it trending!
チョコ先生、
Choco-sensei,
何？
Yes?
いつも優しくて、
You're always so kind,
いつもメルのこと思ってくれて、
always thinking of Mel,
たくさんメルに付き合ってくれる、
and spending so much time with me.
チョコ先生がメルは大好き！
Mel loves you, Choco-sensei!
チョコも、いつもメル様に頼ってばっかりだけど、
Choco too... I'm always relying on Mel-sama,
でも、メル様といて、すごく楽しくて、
but being with Mel-sama is so much fun,
なんか、メル様とずっと一緒にいたいなって思うから、
and I feel like I want to be with you forever,
これからもよろしくね。
so please continue to be with me.
こちらこそ、これからもよろしく！
Likewise, I'm looking forward to it!
あの、チョコ先生、
Um, Choco-sensei,
何？
Yes?
大好き！
I love you!
そんなことされたらチョコ心臓止まっちゃう！
If you do that, Choco's heart will stop!
いいですか？
Are you okay?
もう一回、今度はチョコ先生がして！
One more time, it's Choco-sensei's turn!
ごめん、チョコ嬉しくて、いっぱいおねだりしちゃうかもしれないけど、
Sorry, Choco is so happy, I might ask for too much, but...
メル様...
Mel-sama...
大好き。
I love you.
今の挨拶、今のチョコの挨拶、取らないで！挨拶、おはよーって挨拶！
Don't take that as just a greeting! My greeting, my 'Good morning' greeting!
おはよー、みんな。いろんな意味でおはよー！
Good morning, everyone. Good morning in many ways!
ということで、メルキスって、そんな感じで、
So, that's how MelKiss is,
これからもメルキスをよろしくお願いします！
and we hope for your continued support for MelKiss!
そしてね、残念なお知らせが一つ。
And, there's one piece of sad news.
次の曲で最後になりました。
The next song will be the last one.
ガチ？ガチ。
Really? Really.
でも、嬉しいお知らせが一つ！
But, there's one piece of happy news!
次の曲、なんと重大発表の一つです！
The next song includes a major announcement!
最後まで楽しんでってね！
Please enjoy until the very end!
じゃあ最後まで聴いてってね！それじゃあ！
So please listen until the end! Here we go!
よし！
Alright!
最後まで楽しもう！
Let's enjoy it until the end!
いくわよ！
Here we go!
Chu Chu Chu とろけそうで
Chu Chu Chu, it's melting
Chu Chu Chu 甘く芳醇
Chu Chu Chu, sweet and mellow
Chu Chu Chu 口づけを Choco Melty
Chu Chu Chu, give me a kiss, Choco Melty
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
よっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
ウフーフー！
Woo-hoo!
ほんの少しお疲れな日は
On days when you're just a little tired,
幸せの箱開けちゃおう
let's open the box of happiness.
甘い園の誘惑も
Even the temptations of the sweet garden,
乗ってみるの？
do you want to try getting on?
お疲れ様でした！乾杯！
Thanks for your hard work! Cheers!
カプっと噛みつく君のハート
A quick bite into your heart,
もっともっと好きになってね
please like me more and more.
不器用だけど愛して
I'm clumsy, but please love me.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
最高な日！
The best day!
みんなー！今日は見てくれてありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you for watching today!
メルキスのオリ曲ができましたー！
MelKiss's original song is here!
ノリのいい曲だからいっぱい声出してねー！
It's an upbeat song, so make some noise!
コールもあるからたくさん聞いて覚えてね！
There are calls too, so listen to it a lot and learn them!
私たちと踊りましょう！
Let's dance with us!
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after,
メリメルティな恋となれ
let it be a Mel-Melty love.
仕事キャラメル召し上がれ
Have some work caramel,
甘美なこの物語も
this sweet story too.
ずっとついてきて
Follow me forever,
サニーラッキーな日々を
sunny, lucky days.
君と見つめ合う未来で
In the future where we gaze at each other,
さあ よろしくどうぞ
now, please take care of me.
Chu Chu Chu とろけそうで
Chu Chu Chu, it's melting
Chu Chu Chu 甘く芳醇
Chu Chu Chu, sweet and mellow
Chu Chu Chu ちょっと苦い Choco Melty
Chu Chu Chu, a bit bitter, Choco Melty
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
よっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
ウフーフー！
Woo-hoo!
あ、一息していかない？
Ah, won't you take a breath?
頑張りすぎも毒だし
Working too hard is poison too.
苦くも甘い誘惑も
Even the bitter-sweet temptations,
受け入れててね
please accept them.
心お疲れ様です！オーライ！
Thanks for your heart's hard work! All right!
見てあげるわ 君のハート
I'll look at your heart,
ほんのちょっと照れくさいかな？
is it just a little embarrassing?
私だけを愛して
Love only me.
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
最高な日！
The best day!
メルさーん！この曲で最後だってー！
Mel-san! This is the last song!
もうやだやだー！終わりたくないよー！
No, no, no! I don't want it to end!
やだやだー！終わりたくないよー！
あー！私たちとはしゃぎましょう！
Ah! Let's have fun with us!
いつもいつまでも
Always, forever,
メリメルティな恋かな
is it a Mel-Melty love?
ショコラココアで召し上がれ
Enjoy it with chocolate cocoa,
悪戯なこのレシピを
this mischievous recipe.
もっとついてきて
Follow me more,
ハッピーラッキーな日々を
happy, lucky days.
終わりのないこの未来で
In this endless future,
さあ ずっと続くよ
now, it'll continue forever.
ここにいれることがただただ嬉しくて
I'm just so happy to be here
この大切な時間が止まってほしくて
I want this precious time to stop
メルさんと出会えたこと
Meeting Mel-san
先生に見つけてもらえたこと
Being found by the Sensei (viewers)
甘くて淡い最高の出会いを
A sweet and soft, best encounter
1. 両手広げて
1. Spread both hands
2. 胸に抱きしめて
2. Hold it to your chest
3. 最後は笑顔で
3. Finally, with a smile
ワクワクキラキラドキドキ全て手にして
Get all the excitement, sparkle, and heart-throbs
もしもこの夢が叶うとするならば
If this dream were to come true
幸せの形作って
Creating the shape of happiness
ビターなシュガーでも
Even with bitter sugar
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after,
メリメルティな恋となれ
let it be a Mel-Melty love.
仕事キャラメル召し上がれ
Have some work caramel,
甘美なこの物語も
this sweet story too.
ずっとついてきて
Follow me forever,
サニーラッキーな日々を
sunny, lucky days.
君と見つめ合う未来で
In the future where we gaze at each other,
さあ よろしくどうぞ
now, please take care of me.
Chu Chu Chu とろけそうで
Chu Chu Chu, it's melting
Chu Chu Chu 甘く芳醇
Chu Chu Chu, sweet and mellow
Chu Chu Chu 甘い合言葉
Chu Chu Chu, sweet love words
Chu Chu Chu メロメロで
Chu Chu Chu, madly in love
Chu Chu Chu 刺激的
Chu Chu Chu, stimulating
Chu Chu Chu 口づけを Choco Melty
Chu Chu Chu, give me a kiss, Choco Melty
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
よっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
ウフーフー！
Woo-hoo!
あー イェー！
Ah, yeah!
メルキス 3周年LIVE Xmas Party
MelKiss 3rd Anniversary LIVE Xmas Party